nlyman.com 2015-06-08

# Menswear Clothes And Designer Brands Online - NlyMan.com

### PRIVACY POLICY 

#### Personal data

NLY cares about your privacy and strives to at all times protect your personal data in the best possible way. NLY’s aim is to comply with all applicable laws and regulations for the protection of personal data. This policy will, among other things, help you understand what kind of personal data that NLY collects and how it is used. By approving this privacy policy on the Website in connection with a purchase or the provision of personal data, you agree to the processing of your personal data as described below. 

NLY Scandinavia AB, (”NLY”/”we”), SE556653882201, Box 690, SE-501 13 Borås is responsible as data controller for the processing of your personal data. 

#### Which personal data will we process? 

We will process the personal data that you provide or have provided us with or that we have collected at our Website by way of cookies for the purposes of administering your purchases and fulfilling our obligations to you as our customer. The personal data that NLY processes include your personal identity number, name, gender, e-mail address, purchase-, payment- and order history, credit card number, delivery address, IP-address and phone number.

NLY uses Google’s advertising services. For more information about Google's collection, sharing and use of data, please see Google’s “Privacy & Terms” which you can find _[here](http://www.google.com/intl/en-GB/policies/privacy/partners/)_.

#### How will we use your personal data? 

The data may be used for identification, direct marketing, customer surveys, newsletters and statistics. The data may also be used for sending post, SMS and e-mail to you and for marketing and information via the telephone, unless you have opted out from such communication. You may at any time contact us to opt out against any marketing towards you as customer.

The data may also be used to analyse purchase habits with the purpose of supplying you with relevant information and marketing and to improve the Website, payment methods and payment processes. Processing for the purpose of improving payment methods and payment processes may include processing where your personal data, inter alia your personal identity number, is transferred to other companies within NLY’s group and to third party providers to be included in the basis for the analysis. The personal data may therefore be processed together with data in other registers, e.g. registers for credit reports. 

Your personal identity number will also be processed in connection with a purchase on behalf of (or due to requirements from) third party providers of payment and credit card services that need it for the purpose of obtaining third party credit reports. 

The use of your personal data may result in data being processed together with data in other registers, both within and outside of the EU, and that your personal data is transferred to, and processed by, other companies within NLY’s group for the purposes described above in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. The data may also be processed with data from, or shared with, authorities or our partners e.g. for printing and distribution and third party providers of payment or credit card services. NLY always observes the utmost care for such use.

By approving the policy on the Website in connection with purchases or the provision of personal data, you agree to the transfer of your personal data to countries outside of the EEA. 

If the whole or part of the NLY’s business is sold or integrated with another business, your personal data may be provided to our advisors, any potential buyer or the buyer’s advisor and furthermore be provided to the new owner of the business.

NLY uses Google’s advertising services. For more information about Google's collection, sharing and use of data, please see Google’s “Privacy & Terms” which you can find _[here](http://www.google.com/intl/en-GB/policies/privacy/partners/)_.

#### How will we protect your personal data? 

In order to protect the personal data that we process, we have implemented several security measures. We have implemented security procedures and technical and organisational measures to protect your personal data e.g. certification procedures for web browsers. We furthermore have sufficient firewalls and anti-virus programs in order to protect and prevent unauthorized access to the network. Physical access to the premises where the data is stored is limited and employees are required to be identified in order to gain access. 

NLY furthermore uses e.g. SLL (Secure Socket Layer) which is a protocol for the safe transfer of data over the Internet (or other networks). As a customer, you need to check that SLL is not turned off in the settings of the web browser. With the purpose of preventing any unauthorized access upon processing you credit card number, one-way codes will be used. 

#### How long will my personal data be kept by NLY?

If you provide your consent to being a registered customer/member with NLY, your data will be kept until you deregister. You may at any time deregister from being a customer. If you do not register as a customer/member, your personal data will be kept only for as long as it is necessary to comply with law or in order for NLY to fulfil its obligations towards you, e.g. to complete delivery or warranty obligations.

No matter what, your personal data will never be kept for a period longer than what is permitted in compliance with applicable personal data legislation. 

#### Access to, updating and correction of your personal data 

In accordance with the applicable personal data legislation, you are entitled, once every calendar year, free of charge, to receive information on which of your personal data is processed by us, regardless of how it has been collected. If you wish to receive such information, you can arrange to do so by making a written request to us. According to the applicable personal data legislation, your request shall be duly signed by you and sent by regular mail, see address given on the Website. Thus, it cannot be sent by e-mail. 

NLY wants to ensure that your personal data is correct and updated. If any of the data you provide to NLY is changed, e.g. if you change your e-mail address, name or payment information or if you want to change your user account, please provide NLY with correct details by by sending an e-mail to NLY. You are, at all times, entitled to request that your personal data is corrected, blocked or erased.

Your personal data will not be processed for purposes related to direct marketing if you op-pose such processing. You are, at any time, entitled to withdraw any given consent for the processing of personal data. Such withdrawal may be limited to include only part of the processing, for example that which is connected to direct marketing.

#### Links

The Website may contain links to other websites. This Privacy Policy applies only to the Website. When you are being linked to another website, you should read the privacy policy which applies to that website. Please note that NLY is not responsible for the processing of your personal data by or on other websites.

#### Amendments to the Privacy Policy

NLY reserves the right, at any time, to make amendments to this Privacy Policy to the extent necessary to remedy disturbances or to comply with new legislative or technical requirements. Any amendments to this Privacy Policy will be posted on the Website. 

#### Cookies

We use so called cookies on the NLY’s Website. Cookies are small text files that are saved on your computer and that our web server uses to provide you with access to some of the functions available on the Website. 

There are two main types of cookies: 1) a saved cookie (permanent cookie) which remains on your computer for an indeterminate period of time, 2) a temporary cookie (session cookie) which is stored temporarily in the computer’s memory during the time that you are visiting a website. Session cookies disappear when you close your web browser.

NLY uses cookies to improve the Website for customers e.g. by adapting the Website with regards to the customers’ wishes, choices and interests, help you keep track of which products have been put into your shopping cart and to handle you purchase, make sure that the visitor has logged into the Website so that the customer does not have to log in every time he/she browses a different page, to adjust our services to make sure that you receive advertising which is relevant for you and in order for us to fulfill our obligations in relation to a purchase. 

Permanent cookies are being used, among other things, to store any personal settings at NLY e.g. to make sure that you do not need to redo certain choices made every time you visit the Website and to adapt and make information and marketing as relevant for you as possible. Temporary cookies are being used, among other things, for the purpose of registering statistics for the use of the Website.

By accepting NLY’s general conditions and/or this privacy policy and by using NLY’s Web-site, you agree to the processing of cookies as described above. If you do not accept cookies being used, you can turn off cookies in the security settings of your web browser. You can also set your web browser to ask you each time NLY’s Website tries to place a cookie on your computer. You can also use your web browser to delete previously stored cookies. See your web browser’s help pages for more information. Furthermore, you can at any time delete cookies manually from your hard drive.

Please note that if you choose not to accept cookies, functionality may be limited for some parts of the website and the website may not work as intended, e.g. you will not be able to make a purchase online. 

* * *

PLEASE NOTE! Nothing in the General Conditions affects a Customer’s mandatory statutory rights under applicable local laws, to the extent that such rights apply to such Customer and cannot be limited or excluded.
